I left food money in the cabinet above the oven,
but that's all you're gonna get so you better make it last.
Hey there, Robert.
I'd offer to help you with your bags, but you're a coon.
What's he doing here?
He's your babysitter.
Come on, Grandad.
Me and Riley don't need no babysitter.
We can take care of ourselves.
Yes, not like we're gonna try to kill each other.
Shut up.
Do what Ruckus says and don't mess up my house.
Come on.
Me and this punk fool right here.
OK, first of all, ain't nobody talking while I'm talking,
so shut the fuck up.
My name is Uncle Ruckus, and I will be
a nigger sitting you two until your grandfather retains.
Your granddad picked me because I am a licensed zoologist.
I have studied a variety of wild animals,
and the African male is by far the most savage laconic.
This is an opportunity to observe you
niggers in your natural habitat and collect data.
But be warned, whatever nigger chicory
you got up your sleeves does not affect me.